c21stores.com 2019-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Century 21 Stores | C21

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE GET IT?

Century 21 Department Store, also referred to as C21Stores.com, is committed to protecting your privacy. If you utilize the C21Stores.com website, then you agree to the C21Stores.com Privacy Policy. In order to access the C21Stores.com website you must complete the registration process. C21Stores.com collects guest information in an effort to improve our guest's shopping experience and to communicate with our guests about our products, services and promotions. We collect information such as your name, email and postal address, and credit cards that you provide to us when you place an order, when you submit your information with us or when you participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey. C21Stores.com may use your information collected online to process and fulfill your order and send you any necessary email messages related to your order, and to send membership invitations to your friends. In addition, we maintain a record of your product interests, purchases and whatever else might enable us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience. We also monitor site use and traffic patterns to improve our website design and the products and services we offer. C21Stores.com recognizes that it must maintain and use guest information responsibly.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and in our stores. We may also combine that information with publicly available information we receive from or cross-reference with select partners and others. By combining this information we are better able to communicate with you about our products, special events and promotional purposes and to personalize your shopping experience.

Century 21 Department Store will not rent or sell your email address for any reason. We may disclose information about you to other members of the Century 21 Department Stores corporate family and as required by law, to include a company with which we contract to help us prevent the unauthorized use of credit and gift cards. If at any time you would like us to remove you from our mailing list, [click here to unsubscribe](https://www.c21stores.com/account). You can always update or delete your personal information on our website. Simply [visit My Account](https://www.c21stores.com/account) in the menu at the top of each page on our website and you will be able to edit or change your information. If at any time you would like us to delete any of your personal information on file, just [email C21Stores.com customer service](mailto:customerservice@c21stores.com). Please be sure to include your email address and full name. Or you may [call us at 877-350-2121](tel:+1-877-350-2121).

We may also work with select partners to distribute web advertisements based on your internet browsing patterns. These advertising companies collect anonymous information about your visits to our website through the use of a cookie. This technology allows them to develop our advertising so that it directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you. These partners never collect personally identifiable information, however, if you'd prefer, you may [opt out at any time by clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.

We do not share credit card information with third parties except for the purpose of processing payment for products you've ordered and as required by law. In addition, we may disclose credit card and other information we collect from you with an outside company with which we have contracted for their services to protect against fraud and the unauthorized use of credit and gift cards.

In addition to personal information, we collect information about your visits to and use of the site that is not personally identifiable. For example, our site uses cookies, which are small information files that are sent to your computer and stored on your hard drive. Cookies ease your use of the site, and provide us with information about your use of the site—for example, the pages that you view. If you have registered with us, then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit the C21Stores.com site, by remembering your email address for you when you interact with the site. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent, but if you do not permit your browser to accept cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the features of the site. We may also collect the IP address through which you access the Internet to use our site. Your IP address will typically be provided by your Internet service provider, your employer or the business or institution that provides you with access to the Internet. An IP address is not, by itself, personal information. We may use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which you and other guests visit the sites, and the patterns of site use. We may also combine IP addresses with personal information. To the extent that your IP address is combined with personal information, it will be treated as personal information. The site may also collect non-personal information through other technical methods.

We use the non-personal information collected through technology for a number of purposes, including tracking and enhancing your experience on our site. We also may use the information gathered by technology to analyze the traffic patterns on our site, such as the frequency with which you and others visit various parts of the site. We may send HTML emails to you if you’ve registered with C21Stores.com and those emails may contain data or routines that allow us to determine whether you have opened those emails, clicked on links in those emails or forwarded those emails to others.

We may disclose aggregate, anonymized statistics about the number of visitors to this site or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this site on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page views, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings, and other general information. C21Stores.com uses and stores this type of information, along with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users.

We do not knowingly collect or store personal information from children under 13, even in aggregate. If we learn that we have done so we will endeavor to delete such personal information as soon as possible.

## BUSINESS PARTNERS

We contract with an outside service called Google Analytics to help us better understand your use of C21Stores.com. Google Analytics places cookies on your computer to collect various kinds of information for us related to your use of C21Stores.com, so that we may continue to refine and improve the site for our customers. We do not allow Google Analytics to collect any credit card, user name or password information, nor are they allowed to use data that they collect for us for any other purpose. Additionally, Google Analytics is contractually required to maintain all the information collected for us in strict confidence. In order to utilize the C21Stores.com website, it is necessary that site users allow cookies.

## SECURITY

When ordering with us, we want our customers to feel confident we are using standard industry practices to protect the data stored within our system. On C21Stores.com, we encrypt your credit card number and other information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, which guarantees secure transmission of information.

## NOTE TO CHILDREN

If you are under the age of 18, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to C21Stores.com. C21Stores.com is intended for users who are 18 years of age and older. In the event that we become aware a registered user is under the age of 18, we will delete all details relating to that user’s account.

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Periodically we may update or change our Privacy Policy. We will post updates here so that you are informed of them. Your acceptance of these updates is indicated by your continued use of the website.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy please contact us at:  
Century 21 Department Store Guest Service  
22 Cortlandt Street  
New York, NY 10007
